mikegold4060@gmai l.com

# 27 years old

Singaporean

### Languages

**English** 

Chinese

#### **Assets**

Intelligence

One of your assets

**Passion** 

#### **Interests**

**Table-Tennis, Swimming** Cooking

Passionate Software Engineer with 7+ years of experience in developing Full-Stack & Mobile Development. Skilled at writing clear, readable code that is easy to maintain and troubleshoot. Experienced in working with both small and large teams across multiple projects and companies.

## Computer skills

Full-Stack, React.js. Node.js, JavaScript, MongoDB, HTML/CSS

Android & iOS, React-Native, Flutter, Dart, Java, Kotlin

#### **Agile Product Management**

#### **Education**



2017

From September 2013 to January Computer Science University of Ohio Athens, OH

## Work experience

#### Full-Stack & Mobile Engineer

From February 2022 to September 2023 iTechArt Group London UK

- Developed and maintained 10+ front-ends focused on user experience.
- Wrote front-end code, back-end code, integrated 4+ with frameworks and APIs, and utilized multiple CLI tools and configuration GUI's.
- Created and updated 2 websites with a focus on creating an exceptional user experience.
- Utilized and implemented 5+ attractive, responsive, and mobile-friendly website contexts and elements.
- Created informative and effective documentation, reports, and inline comments on 100% of code/work accomplished.
- Developed and maintained mobile applications resulting in a 20% increase in user engagement and a 30% increase in app downloads.
- Implemented new features and functionality for Android applications using Java and Kotlin languages.
- Collaborated with cross-functional teams to design and develop mobile applications that met business requirements.

# **Full-Stack Engineer**

From April 2020 to November 2021 Intive London, UK

- Built 30+ custom interfaces using the Periodic API
- Implemented 14 new features as defined and scoped by a product team of 12
- Collaborated with 2 different development teams on 4 new project designs and feature improvements
- Diagnosed and fixed report functionality issues by troubleshooting
- Suggested 20+ improvements to product design and functionality as informed by user-experience reporting

# Work experience

## Full-Stack Developer

From May 2017 to January 2020 Wintech Digital Newcastle upon Tyne, UK

- Implemented rich user experiences by creating 30+ new features utilizing HTML/JS/CSS.
- Developed and maintained 20+ REST APIs writing documentation using OpenAPI specifications.
- Collaborated with 2 engineering teams on domain, design, and code testing for 8+ projects.
- Followed industry best practices, company best practices, and learned 3 new technologies.
- SKILLS: JavaScript, HTML, CSS, React.js, Node.js, MongoDB, MaterialUI Rest APIs GitFlow

## **Skills**

Excellent written and oral communication skills		5
Development Humor		